<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Notebooks on </title>
    <link>https://argandov.github.io/notebooks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Notebooks on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 21:06:05 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://argandov.github.io/notebooks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Compartmentalization Virtual Machine setup</title>
      <link>https://argandov.github.io/notebooks/isolation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 21:06:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argandov.github.io/notebooks/isolation/</guid>
      <description>Important: This following guide assumes your activities will be low-risk, so the isolation is kept at some degree lightly. If you have some advanced and specific needs, this guide may come short and you may need to do some more research. In this case, we would need to take some extra steps to fully isolate our environment, and this post would become very extensive, so keep that in mind.
There are tons of tools available to effectively compartmentalize our virtual machines (From Type 1 or &amp;ldquo;bare metal&amp;rdquo; like VMware&amp;rsquo;s ESXi or even Qubes OS to Type 2 or &amp;ldquo;hosted&amp;rdquo; like virtual Box or VMware).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Examine files in transit from pcap files in Linux</title>
      <link>https://argandov.github.io/notebooks/mono-networkminer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 21:06:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argandov.github.io/notebooks/mono-networkminer/</guid>
      <description>In order for us to have a friendly interface for analizing network capture files (pcap), it&amp;rsquo;s very useful to have monitoring tools like Network Miner, which lets us extract the data in transit as it happened at the time of the capture. It also allows us to &amp;ldquo;sniff&amp;rdquo; communications in real time but for this time we will only be using it for reading an already existing .pcap file.
What is Network Miner anyways?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Terminal: Keeping a neat and clean workspace</title>
      <link>https://argandov.github.io/notebooks/windowsterminal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 21:06:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argandov.github.io/notebooks/windowsterminal/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to open sessions, monitoring your network or communicate between servers/hosts, organization is key for an agile mind.
While there are lots of options to establish a connection between hosts (Like Termius, PuTTY, or even the original terminal), I found the new Windows Terminal app to be just perfect for handling multiple sessions at once.
In this article, we’ll explore some of the features and settings for the WT, and in this particular demonstration we will be using a Linux Virtual Machine as a guest to connect to, but we can set up automatic SSH sessions to routers, switches, FTP, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Firefox hardening quick guide</title>
      <link>https://argandov.github.io/notebooks/firefox_hardening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 21:06:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://argandov.github.io/notebooks/firefox_hardening/</guid>
      <description>Note: This was originally intended as a quick personal benchmark, but decided to upload it in case it is useful for someone else. Go ahead with caution and do your research.
The results of this guidelines render only a casual-use Firefox configuration. If you have special privacy/anonimity needs, or are concerned about sofisticated attack vectors, then please do not use Firefox (Or use it with other privacy-enhancing services/softwares). Do your own modifications and research as needed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
